Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
- Hello?
- Hey. it's Donny. Where are you?
I'm in the loo.
- I've got a nosebleed.
- Oh?
- Are you hungover?
- What?
You told me you get nosebleeds
when you're hungover.
What do you want. Donny?
I'm in reception
with. er. Myrtle Clarke.
Fuck.
Okay.
- Myrtle.
- Oh.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's fine.
Er. are you okay? You've got...
Oh. yeah. I just. erm.
I just had a nosebleed this morning.
Erm. okay. let me show you around.
and then we'll get you
set up at your desk.
You've met Donny. He's our
receptionist/concierge/mother superior.
Er. let me show you the nice bits first.
Well. we're a fiduciary
pension fund manager.
which means organisations give us
their pension money to invest.
So like. private companies.
government departments. unions too.
for lower income workers.
We take that money.
and we invest it. and. erm...
Well. that's pretty much
all you need to know.
So. this is the client-prepping
meeting area.
Which means
that's where all the good biscuits are.
It's literally the only reason
why I brought you here.
Oh. wow!
I know. right.
But don't let them catch you in here.
It's a sacking offence.
And this is us.
Oh. that is the Investment Committee.
They're the team that get paid
the mega-bucks
to decide what we invest in.
I. er. really like sugar.
And plus. it's free.
Free sugar. you know
what I mean?
Myrtle. this is Luke.
He works with us on the trade processing.
Nice to meet you. Myrtle.
So. this is it. Trade processing.
Jewel in the crown
of the operations team.
On my first day on the job.
the person who showed me around.
told me that every day
you spend in operations
is a day of your career you've wasted.
And also your life.
Yeah. that... that was me.
Yeah. I thought I'd pass it on.
Erm. thanks?
No worries. The trick of the job is...
Not to die of boredom.
Phone jammers on.
Level 27. doors opening.
Hi.
Disconnect the call now.
Security's been taken out.
Er. let me get a geek
to set up your computer.
Yeah?
Hello?
Everybody listen to me
right fucking now!
- Get away from the computer!
- On your feet!
Hands in the air!
- Stand up!
- Move away from the fucking desk!
Hands in the air!
Hands in the fucking air now!
Faster! Go! Go!
- Toilets clear.
- Hey!
Up! You! Hands!
Ladies and gentlemen.
if you do exactly what I say
when I say it. you won't get hurt.
If you don't do what I say when I say it.
you will be shot.
If you have any communication devices
on you.
phones. tablets.
I want you to take them out.
I want you to hold them high
in the air above your head. Do it now.
Once you have your phones
in the air above your head.
I want you to move slowly
towards the conference room. this way.
When you get
to the conference room...
Move. Move.
I need you to put your devices
in this grey bin one by one.
- Move.
- Move! In the air!
- Above you head.
- One by one.
If you have phones.
put them in the air.
Above your head. Move!
Move. Above your head.
Keep moving.
Phones above your heads.
Move!
That's a SIG Sauer MPX-K.
You fire that off in here
and everyone will hear it
from the fifth floor to the tenth.
And the people in the buildings opposite.
Security will lock us down
and you will be trapped here
before you can even get to the lifts.
You're not stupid enough
to shoot that in here.
I doubt you even bothered loading it.
We don't have to fire our guns
to kill you with them.
Get him secure.
- Keep moving.
- Move!
Just move! Move!
Move!
Don't look at him. just move!
- Keep moving.
- Move!
- Move now.
- Get up. follow them.
Come on. get on with it.
Move it!
Hands! Hands!
Right. everybody on the floor.
Keep your hands above your heads
where I can see them.
Slowly.
Conference room's secure.
Antenna up
on the satellite phone.
Location secure.
Anyone in the trade processing team.
stand up.
Why'd you tell her to sit down?
It... it's her first day.
She's an intern. She... she...
She's what?
You've got access to the trading system?
What about the rest of you?
Who's the most senior?
Erm. that's me.
You two. come here.
Take me to your desks. now.
Everyone else. stay down.
Take a seat.
This has got the details
of six trades on it.
Source accounts.
destination accounts. sizes.
I want you to load them all up
into the trading system.
Er. no. that won't...
that won't work. I...
Just load up the trades.
All right. yeah.
This is over £4 billion.
Look. these are people's pensions.
This is social workers.
- police. doctors...
- Enter the trades.
Right.
Erm...
Shit.
I'm so sorry.
Erm. sorry.
Shit. sorry. erm...
You can do this.
- They're caught in traffic. too?
- No. Thameslink.
Three cancelled trains and the next trains
were so packed. I couldn't get on.
Yeah. I got stuck in a cab for 40 minutes.
I don't think
that's gonna do anything. Milo.
Why the fuck
did they get rid of the buttons?
I'm late for the bloody
Investment Committee.
Level 27. doors opening.
Doors closing.
Incoming.
Where's Donny?
I'm not sure.
Temp agency sent me.
Phones! Now!
Get on your knees.
Okay. Erm...
that's all done. It's loading.
Commit the trades.
- I can't. I...
- Commit them.
USB.
Trades have gone through.
Get them signed off
by the committee.
Everyone with authorisation
to sign off trades. raise your hands.
The system needs three people
to sign off a trade?
You. go and get your laptop
from the sideboard.
Six new trades have just been entered
into your trading system.
I want you to approve them all...
and send them along.
You're clearing out our cash accounts?
Hang on a second!
That's people's pensions...
What's your name?
George Cartwright.
Now. tell me. George Cartwright.
would you say it's an intelligent man
who argues with an intruder
holding a semi-automatic assault weapon?
No.
Approve the trades.
You're next.
You'll never get away with this.
It's not us who holds the money.
it's our custodian bank.
- And as soon as they...
- Just sign them off.
Right. We need one more of you.
How about the afternoon shift?
All done here.
Trades should be pinging back to you now.
Received.
Trades have been approved.
I... I can't...
They need to be checked by a second member
of the... of the team.
I... I can't do anything.
Good job we brought you along then.
Erm...
Okay. that... that's it. All done.
The trades have been sent
to the custodian bank.
Yeah. but they'll know that we've never
sent money to those accounts before.
so they're gonna call
and ask what's going on.
And you'll be here to tell them.
So we wait.
Doors opening.
Where's Donny?
Oh. I don't know.
I just got sent by the temp agency.
Here's your morning's post
and parcels and. er.
assorted bollocks.
You got a name. then?
Claire.
Oh. lovely!
My... my daughter's a Claire.
- Proper English name.
- It's French.
You got kids?
Yeah. two.
Boy and a girl.
Lovely.
All right. erm...
See you later.
Wait!
Forgot one.
Doors closing.
Hello. Lochmill Capital.
Claire speaking. How can I help?
You ready?
This is it. Custodian bank.
Received. Keep 'em on hold.
The custodian bank's on the line.
When that rings. I want you to answer
and put it on speaker.
I want you to assure them
that all the trades are legit.
No heroics.
no secret messages. understand?
Mmm-hmm.
Once you've assured them.
I want you to ask them
to transfer the money immediately.
Understand?
Yes.
Are you ready?
Put them through.
Putting them through now.
It's gonna. it's gonna go to voicemail.
Hello...
erm. Lochmill Capital. How can I help?
Hello?
Sorry. er. Zara?
All right. Warren. Er...
Luke has...
just nipped to the loo.
You all right?
Yeah. Er. you all right?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. Yeah. I'm just erm...
just really hungover.
I... I went out with erm. Luke and Chee
to The Gladstone last night.
Oh yeah? Late one?
Chee blew us off for a Tinder.
It's just getting old. you know.
it's fucking hangovers...
Tell me about it.
Erm. I just got the trades
you guys sent through.
I've never seen these accounts before.
BVI. right? What are they?
Er. it's just.
erm. er. er. some new
hedge funds we're getting into.
Pretty big amounts
for new hedge fund investments.
Four billion.
Yep.
Yeah. yeah. well it's just a.
a bunch of funds from a manager
we're already invested with.
Erm. I mean.
you know what Cartwright's like.
price. cut-price management fees
for seed capital.
he's. he's all over it...
Yeah. That's Cartwright.
You got all the AML in order?
Yeah.
erm listen. I. I was supposed to...
send these over yesterday but we sort of.
left early for the pub.
But if they don't go through ASAP
I'm gonna be in some...
serious shit. So. if you could please just
put them through
as soon as you put the phone down. please?
Yeah. yeah...
I just need to check something.
Zara?
- Yeah?
- We're all good.
I'll put them through today.
Brilliant. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
No worries. Take care.
Okay. Bye.
Okay. that's it. He's sending them over.
You can er.
go? Now?
We're not leaving till we see
the money arrive in our account.
Well erm. that could take hours.
Fifteen to thirty minutes if your pal
at the bank puts the trades through now.
We wait.
Hey.
Hey...
we can signal.
Why not?
Just let them take
the money and leave.
But how do we know they're going to leave?
How do we know they're not gonna
kill us all before they go?
Why would they do that?
Because we're witnesses.
At least if the police turn up we.
we've got a chance.
Nobody move!
Out the way!
Did anyone
in the other building see you?
If someone saw you. tell me now.
You'll be safer that way.
But if you say no.
the police turn up.
then we're in a hostage situation.
and I will kill you.
Understand?
So...
did someone see you?
- He said no one saw.
- You believe him?
No. He was lying.
Two minutes since I caught him at it.
If I'm right we need to leave now.
Well. we abort
and the trade might not go through.
We need to make a decision.
What's going on?
- We might have to abort.
- Abort?
Are you fucking nuts?
What if they call back?
- What if they don't?
- We planned for this!
The plan was.
if a message gets out. we abort.
We walk out of here.
first thing they do is cancel the trades.
We don't know if a message got out.
Wait! Burly. run a check
on the building opposite for activity.
Twenty-sixth floor
of the Leadenhall.
Three people were at the window.
They're watching us. They spotted me.
We need to abort.
- It's already four minutes since they saw.
- Wait.
Money's been transferred.
Lock and leave. Now!
Get up!
Now! Into the conference room.
- Quick!
- Move!
Control. Foxtrot.
Sierra One. Receive.
Foxtrot.
Sierra One. Control...
Control. Foxtrot.
Sierra One. Receive.
Armed Police! Armed Police!
Foxtrot.
Sierra Three. Control...
Control. Foxtrot.
Sierra Three. Copy that.
News coming into us now
- of an incident in London's Square Mile...
- a few of the streets
around the city skyscraper
have been closed off
- and evacuated...
- We saw a number of
casualties being loaded into ambulances...
Lochmill Capital
has many billions
of pension fund assets under management.
Single file. single file.
Keep it moving. Keep it moving.
Keep it moving.
Stay calm. Just keep it moving.
What do you think they're talking about?
Probably how much shit the company's in.
Whether they'll need us all to sign NDAs.
NDAs? Why?
Think about it.
Miss Dunne?
I'm DCI Rhys Covaci.
I'm the senior investigating officer.
I thought I'd come over and say hello.
Hi.
Shall we pop next door?
- Yeah. okay.
- Okay.
- Can I have the room please. guys?
- Sure.
Ta.
How are you feeling?
Erm...
just a bit... dazed. I don't know.
All feels like a bit of a dream.
You're in shock. Don't worry. it'll pass.
And it's totally normal.
It's not every day you go through
something like this. right?
You been checked over by the medic?
It was all okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
- All right.
That's good to hear.
First up.
sorry for keeping you all here.
it was the nearest place
my colleagues could find for triage.
No. no. it's fine.
I er. I always wondered
what the other floors in here looked like.
It turns out they look exactly like ours
except maybe someone
stole all the furniture.
Kind of ironic
considering the circumstances.
We're working on getting you all
out of here as soon as we can.
We've arranged to have you taken over
to Bishopsgate for your interviews.
You and your colleagues here have been
ID-ed as potential significant witnesses.
- It's why we're keeping you separate.
- Okay.
It just means you interacted
with the thieves more than everybody else.
so whatever you can tell us
will be invaluable.
- Okay?
- Yeah. sure.
All right.
Is there anything else you want
while I'm here? Anything you need?
Erm. my. my co-workers.
the ones who were injured.
- do you know...
- They're fine.
I've spoken to the paramedics.
Broken bones. bruises.
but nothing life changing.
Okay.
They're already at the Royal London.
They'll be back home today. tomorrow.
Nothing to worry about.
I heard what you did.
Taking the phone call from the bank?
It's brave.
Smart.
And I think maybe you saved a few lives.
If their plan had gone wrong. you know...
You did the right thing.
You...
you having a nosebleed?
Oh. God. Erm.
I had... oh.
I had one this morning.
I thought it had erm...
Do you mind if I go to the toilet to...
- Yeah. Sure. of course.
- My nose.
Thanks.
PC Hussain will accompany you.
Okay. thanks.
- What do you mean?
- The whole of legal.
Marianne. Judith. Those other two.
They were all going nuts.
You didn't see them.
Hi.
Ow!
Oh. it's just a nosebleed.
I'm just... gonna...
So. what happened?
Just what I said.
They were all on their phones till they...
when Marianne went and spoke
to the head cop or whoever
and then she rushed off.
They let her out of the building.
He must have given her the nod.
She's getting all the company's ducks
in a row.
Confidentiality clauses. maybe.
Damage limitation mode's
already kicked in.
Yeah. I ain't surprised.
Clients are gonna be
heading for the hills.
Yeah. I don't think it's
the clients that they're worried about.
- So. what then?
- Isn't it obvious?
They're worried it was an inside job.
Inside job?
Come on. Chee.
They knew everything about our operation.
Our protocols.
how our trade management system works.
investment committee sign off.
custodian bank. all of it.
I mean. someone must have told them.
So you think it's one of us?
It makes sense. right?
How else could they do it?
Well. if one of us was involved.
that's horrible.
One of us would put the whole office
through that?
Yeah. but for four billion though.
Split. what eight. nine ways?
That's half a billion each. Wouldn't you?
Still. it should make it easy
to figure out who the inside man was.
Yeah. whoever turns up tomorrow
in a Ferrari.
Or doesn't turn up at all.
Police confirmed earlier today
that the amount stolen from the pensions
was in excess of £4 billion.
making it the largest armed robbery
in British history.
If I was planning this
and wanted an inside man.
I'd go for someone
on the trade processing team.
Find the money.
find the thieves...
The level they're operating at.
ex-army. maybe state actors.
There's thousands of people
losing their pensions.
These are cold-blooded people.
Stay where you are. I'm gonna come over.
You gonna tell me how you're involved?
Are you in danger. Zara?
The jaded office worker
stumbling through life.
The people that I am dealing with.
want me dead!
It wasn't the thieves
trying to pick you up back there.
It was MI5.
There are more important things
going on here than you're aware of.
My investigation's being set up to fail.
There's another bloody layer.
You're in the big league now.
It's about the end game.
And the million different ways
you might not survive it.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm